historio.us 2019-03-12

# privacy policy - historious

Here at historious we take your privacy very seriously. We have tried to make sure our privacy policy is accessible to and understandable by everyone. 

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the historious website and services, post a link to the historious website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times, its source and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties. 

We will never automatically send you third party information/offers you do not want, or share your email address or other data with third parties. 

We will also never share the content of your historified pages with anyone without your permission, although we might use the URLs of pages to compile anonymized lists of popular or new links and the URL of your personal historious for sitemap and other listing or indexing purposes. 

historious reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website or public communication channels so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this website, you can send an e-mail, in English, to [support@historio.us](mailto:support@historio.us). 

Effective Date: June 1, 2010
